{
    "subject": "resource/Poseidon_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of the film Poseidon is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9729026556015015,
            "question": "Is the film Poseidon spoken in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9163448810577393,
            "question": "What language is the film Poseidon in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8055267333984375,
            "question": "Is English the only language used in Poseidon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7627658247947693,
            "question": "Are there any other languages spoken in Poseidon besides English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7514930963516235,
            "question": "Can viewers understand Poseidon if they speak English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6849242448806763,
            "question": "Does the film Poseidon rely heavily on English dialogue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6506505012512207,
            "question": "If you enjoy films with English dialogue, would you likely enjoy Poseidon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6233265399932861,
            "question": "Is knowing English necessary to understand the plot of Poseidon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5632158517837524,
            "question": "What is the primary language of communication in Poseidon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41239526867866516,
            "question": "Would someone who doesn't speak English need subtitles to watch Poseidon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the film Poseidon is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5367_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary language of communication in Poseidon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5367_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is knowing English necessary to understand the plot of Poseidon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5367_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you enjoy films with English dialogue, would you likely enjoy Poseidon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5367_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5367_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the text mentions \"English (UK)\" and \"Australian English,\" it doesn't explicitly state that the language of the movie *Poseidon* is English.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents mentions that \"Poseidon\" is an Action/Adventure movie directed by Wolfgang Petersen and based on a novel. While it does not explicitly state the language of the film, the context suggests that the English language would be used for the dialogue and narration as the movie is being discussed in relation to English (UK) pronunciation guidance. Therefore, it can be inferred that the film \"Poseidon\" likely has English as its primary spoken language."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text describes the film as an \"Action/Adventure movie directed by Wolfgang Petersen\"  and mentions a plot involving characters guided by an \"ex-marshal.\" These details strongly suggest that the primary language of the film would be English, given its genre and setting.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}